{
    "subject": "resource/The_Neighbourhood",
    "predicate": "ontology/alias",
    "object": "THE NBHD (abbreviation)",
    "human_readable": "The alias of The Neighbourhood is THE NBHD.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7001535296440125,
            "question": "Is THE NBHD commonly used by fans of The Neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.546746551990509,
            "question": "What are the initials of The Neighbourhood's alias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2814004719257355,
            "question": "What is another name for The Neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26550501585006714,
            "question": "Is THE NBHD a different name for a musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25824928283691406,
            "question": "Which abbreviation represents The Neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2495107650756836,
            "question": "How is The Neighbourhood sometimes referred to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2094624638557434,
            "question": "Can you provide a different name for The Neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1788327693939209,
            "question": "What is the short form of The Neighbourhood's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16254402697086334,
            "question": "Does The Neighbourhood have an alternate name used in some contexts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1287417709827423,
            "question": "What is the shortened version of The Neighbourhood's band name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The alias of The Neighbourhood is THE NBHD.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5715_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does The Neighbourhood have an alternate name used in some contexts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5715_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the short form of The Neighbourhood's name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5715_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide a different name for The Neighbourhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5715_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5715_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe context information explicitly mentions that the band is sometimes recognized as \u201cTHE NBHD\u201d, which supports the statement that an alias for The Neighbourhood is THE NBHD."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}